{
    "subject": "resource/Escort_(band)",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "The hometown of Escort (band) is United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9090803265571594,
            "question": "Is Escort (band) a local or international band based on their hometown?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.817609429359436,
            "question": "What country is the hometown of Escort (band) located in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7914827466011047,
            "question": "In what part of the world is Escort (band)'s hometown situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7097876071929932,
            "question": "Where is Escort (band) from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6726036071777344,
            "question": "Does Escort (band)'s hometown have a rich music history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3490755558013916,
            "question": "What type of music is Escort (band) known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32947084307670593,
            "question": "Which nation considers Escort (band) as their own?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16040553152561188,
            "question": "Can you name another famous musical group from the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1212010532617569,
            "question": "What are some characteristics of places in the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11030402779579163,
            "question": "How has the United States influenced popular music?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The hometown of Escort (band) is United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9219_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some characteristics of places in the United States?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9219_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name another famous musical group from the United States?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9219_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which nation considers Escort (band) as their own?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9219_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9219_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9219_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9219_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9219_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9219_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9219_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9219_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9219_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9219_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9219_56.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information mentions that \"Hometown: Brooklyn,\" which is a part of the United States. Therefore, the query \"The hometown of Escort (band) is United States\" is supported by the given documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}